<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/doctors/doctor1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/doctors/doctor1/</guid>
      <description>Speciality: Acupuncture and Chinese Herbal Medicine Qualifications: BHlthSc (Hons-ChinMed), RCMP, PhD Dr George Lenon is a founder of GL Natural Healthcare and he is qualified practitioner both in Australia and overseas. He began his Traditional Chinese Medicine journey many years ago. After graduating from Chinese medicine at Victoria University, Dr. George Lenon then went on to earn his PhD at RMIT University with his internationally recognized research in allergies (ie. Hayfever) and weight loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/doctors/doctor2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/doctors/doctor2/</guid>
      <description>Speciality: Chinese Medicine Qualifications: Bachelors in Chinese Medicine &amp;amp; Human Biology, RCMP Dr Conan Cole cites his early memories of flicking through his mothers nursing textbooks as the beginnings of his keen interest in biological sciences and the workings of the human body. This along with extensive world travel, interest in other cultures, empathy for others and many years working with his hands. Eventually combined to his undertaking the lifelong learning commitment of being a caregiver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/doctors/doctor3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/doctors/doctor3/</guid>
      <description>Speciality: Acupuncture and Chinese Herbal Medicine Qualifications: BHlthSc &amp;amp; BAppSc (ChinMed) Dr SHIQI (Rose) LUO is a responsible, enthusiastic and professional registered Chinese medicine practitioner who aims to provide the best quality of care to every patient. Rose graduated from RMIT University and obtained a double degree in Health sciences and Chinese Medicine with Distinction. She is currently doing her Ph.D. degree at RMIT University. She is bringing her experience from her internship in one of the most famous Chinese medicine hospitals in Nanjing China and received ‘Jasmine scholarship’ that offered from Jiangsu Province as a result of her outstanding performance during the internship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/doctors/doctor4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/doctors/doctor4/</guid>
      <description>Speciality: Acupuncture and Chinese Herbal Medicine Qualifications: BHlthSc &amp;amp; BAppSc (ChinMed) Dr. Chung is registered Chinese Medicine Practitioner with the Australian Health Practitioner Regulation Agency. Being a daughter of a TCM practitioner, her enthusiasm with TCM developed very early, as she was helping in her father’s clinic during her summer holidays. By witnessing how her dad helps with different types of patients with various conditions, she was determined to follow her dad’s footpath for helping patients with her extensive knowledge in TCM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/doctors/doctor5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/doctors/doctor5/</guid>
      <description>Speciality: Chiropractics Qualifications: BHSc(Chiro), MClinChiro Dr Suhair Shahwan is a graduate doctor from the USA in Chiropractic and Podiatric medicine Dr Suhair Shahwan is a graduate doctor from the USA in Chiropractic and Podiatric medicine with over 10 years of experience in both professions. Dr Shahwan is fully licensed in the USA and Australia. Dr Shahwan is currently an attending supervising clinician at RMIT university. She is a member of the American Podiatric Medical Association and the American Chiropractic Association.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/services/acupuncture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/services/acupuncture/</guid>
      <description>Chinese Acupuncture for Health and Fertility in CBD, Docklands, Westmeadows and surrounding areas Considered to be one of the most popular in the natural treatments healthcare sector, acupuncture has been shown to treat patients who are afflicted with a wide range of conditions. This is already found to be a thriving approach to healthcare as patients are given a holistic and organic alternative to the treatment of disease and illness, linking body, mind and emotions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/services/chiropractics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/services/chiropractics/</guid>
      <description>Chiropractors focus on the intimate relationship the between the nervous system and the spine. biomechanical and structural derangement of the spine can enjoy the nervous system. Therefore, Chiropractic treatment can restore the structural integrity of the spine, Reduce pressure on the sensitive neurological tissue, and consequently Improve the health of the the the individual. Chiropractic deals with the nervous system by means clustering clustering of the Assessing and treating a spine by correcting the Subluxations and to the surrounding muscles Providing therapy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/services/consultation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/services/consultation/</guid>
      <description>At your first visit, our practitioners will need a thorough understanding of your health conditions. We may assess your current health by asking range of comprehensive questions about any illness, medical history, lifestyle and diet. We also use techniques such as blood pressure testing, pulse palpating, face and tongue observation to ascertain your health status. Chiropractic or Osteopath or TCM, diagnostic techniques such as pulse palpating, face and tongue observation will also be used to ascertain your health status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/services/cupping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/services/cupping/</guid>
      <description>Cupping is an ancient Chinese therapy in which a cup is applied to the skin and the pressure in the cup is reduced (either by heat or suction) in order to draw and hold skin and superficial muscles inside the cup. It is based on the meridian theory of the body. Cupping can remove any stagnation in the body and open the meridians so that Qi (energy) can flow freely. It can also help rejuvenate certain meridians and organs that are not functioning at their best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/services/massage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/services/massage/</guid>
      <description>Chinese therapeutic massage is often used to treat sports injuries and other problems affecting the musculoskeketal system. It also provides benefits to people who are under stress, suffered from poor sleep and headaches. Our practitioner may apply a series of specific manipulative techniques, including the use of hands, limbs or other body parts on your respective body surface using varying degrees of force to bring about therapeutic responses (beyond normal relaxation associated with massage).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/services/medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/services/medicine/</guid>
      <description>Herbal Chinese Medicine in Westmeadows and the Glenroy area

Herbal medicine is vast and considered to be the backbone of traditional Chinese medicine. Traditionally, it involves boiling raw herbs for hours, with the subsequent mixture being reduced to concentrated broth. The active ingredients are then taken as a drink. Our clinic offers remedial herbal remedies that are easily brewed in water for a natural therapy. Every patient&amp;rsquo;s condition is unique and so the herbal formula is an individual combination that suits their exact needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/services/moxibustion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/services/moxibustion/</guid>
      <description>Moxibustion is a healing techniques of Traditional Chinese medicine which employed across the diverse traditions of acupuncture and oriental medicine for over 2,000 years. In modern times, both methods are usually used to complement acupuncture with needles but they may be used independently. Moxibustion share the principle of using heat to stimulate circulation and break up congestion or stagnation of blood and Qi. Moxibustion is more closely related to acupuncture as it is applied to specific acupuncture points, while cupping may be used over acupuncture points or elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/en/services/osteothapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/services/osteothapy/</guid>
      <description>Focusing on how skeleton, joints, muscles, nerves, circulation, connective tissue and internal organs function as a holistic unit, osteopathy provides patients with a wide range of stretches and massages to relieve tension from soft tissue. Osteopathy focuses on how the skeleton, joints, muscles, nerves, circulation, connective tissue and internal organs function as a holistic unit. Using skilled evaluation, diagnosis and a wide range of hands-on techniques, osteopaths can identify important types of dysfunction in your body.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>